<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Devlogs on jMonkeyEngine</title>
    <link>/devlog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Devlogs on jMonkeyEngine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/devlog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JMonkeyEngine version 3.3.2 is here!</title>
      <link>/devlog/jme332/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/devlog/jme332/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After 3 months of beta testing, the Java game engine&amp;rsquo;s long-awaited v3.3 release arrived on 30 March.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With it came exciting new features:  AppState ids, light-probe blending, a better ragdoll control, and an animation system rewritten from the ground up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As often happens, a few key bugfixes missed the cutoff for v3.3.0-stable. In its wake, the JMonkeyEngine team came together and identified a handful of existing fixes that could be safely backported into v3.3.  With the help of volunteers, candidate builds received extensive testing on multiple platforms.  Their efforts culminated in version 3.3.2-stable, a production-ready patch release from the v3.3 line.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jMonkeyStore is Now Open!</title>
      <link>/devlog/new-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 06:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/devlog/new-store/</guid>
      <description>After years of requests and attempts, a software store (a.k.a an asset store) for jmonkey has finally been created and is now open to registration. Everybody can register and submit their software!
https://store.jmonkeyengine.org/   Currently only free open-source software can be submitted. Once we have the sponsorship required for the legal documentation and setup fees we will be able to allow selling (payment required to use it) and sponsoring (pay the developer if you want to as a thank you) software.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
