<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jMonkeyEngine</title>
    <link>https://jmonkeyengine.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on jMonkeyEngine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jmonkeyengine.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Minie Physics Library Version 1.4 Released!</title>
      <link>https://jmonkeyengine.org/blog/minie14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmonkeyengine.org/blog/minie14/</guid>
      <description>Minie version 1.4 is an exciting new add-on for the JMonkeyEngine (JME) game engine.
  Minie provides an open-source physics engine for desktop games. It gives software developers using JME access to the proven technology of the Bullet Physics SDK version 2.89, including:
 rigid-body dynamics, soft bodies, collision detection, vehicle and character controllers, ray and sweep tests, and dynamic constraints.  Minie incorporates DynamicAnimControl technology for ragdoll simulation and inverse kinematics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBR Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://jmonkeyengine.org/showcase/pbr_tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmonkeyengine.org/showcase/pbr_tutorial/</guid>
      <description>A continuing YouTube series helping users take leap from using the regular Lighting.j3md material to PbrLighting.j3md.
First part of my tutorial series in which I explain how to use jmonkeyengine&amp;rsquo;s Physically Based Rendering pipeline. Intended for people who already understand how to use the regular Lighting.j3md shader, but have no idea how PBR works.
Second part of my tutorial series in which I explain how to use jmonkeyengine&amp;rsquo;s Physically Based Rendering pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mythruna</title>
      <link>https://jmonkeyengine.org/showcase/mythruna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmonkeyengine.org/showcase/mythruna/</guid>
      <description>Mythruna (myth + rune + a) is a game under development attempting to combine serious role playing elements with an endless, living, and completely modifiable randomly generated sandbox world. When completed, Mythruna will be a unique gaming experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skullstone</title>
      <link>https://jmonkeyengine.org/showcase/skullstone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmonkeyengine.org/showcase/skullstone/</guid>
      <description>Skullstone – a retro styled grid-based dungeon crawler RPG inspired by the good old titles such as Dungeon Master, Stonekeep, Eye of Beholder and many other classics.
In a few words – a party of mercenaries explore a dungeon. They fight monsters, solve puzzles, find equipment, gather experience and level up while progressing through increasingly difficult levels. And there’s a story behind all that, are you ready to discover the truth behind Skullstone ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lightspeed Frontier</title>
      <link>https://jmonkeyengine.org/showcase/ls_frontier/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 06:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmonkeyengine.org/showcase/ls_frontier/</guid>
      <description>Leave everything behind and try your hand at captaining a ship on the frontier of the galaxy. Customize it piece by piece to tackle whatever adventures await you. Take on crime lords and space pirates in battle, undercut corporations that are monopolizing business, influence the galactic stock market, and become the most successful captain you can be.
In this sci-fi adventure sandbox game, you have the opportunity to explore and influence the universe around you and make your own path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spoxel</title>
      <link>https://jmonkeyengine.org/showcase/spoxel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 06:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmonkeyengine.org/showcase/spoxel/</guid>
      <description>Explore, customize, and build across the world of Spoxel as you fight the otherworlders who have subjugated the land and forced the grounders below the surface. Use runes to construct custom powerful spells to use in your adventure or infuse weapons and armor with rare resources to create legendary items of power. Explore an infinite world and delve into other dimensions while you build a base to establish a foothold of power and defend it from your enemies!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jMonkeyStore is Now Open!</title>
      <link>https://jmonkeyengine.org/blog/new-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 06:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmonkeyengine.org/blog/new-store/</guid>
      <description>After years of requests and attempts, a software store (a.k.a an asset store) for jmonkey has finally been created and is now open to registration. Everybody can register and submit their software!
https://jmonkeystore.com/  Currently only free open-source software can be submitted. Once we have the sponsorship required for the legal documentation and setup fees we will be able to allow selling (payment required to use it) and sponsoring (pay the developer if you want to as a thank you) software.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>