<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on jMonkeyEngine</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on jMonkeyEngine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sgold interviews Daniel Perano</title>
      <link>/blog/interview-danielp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/interview-danielp/</guid>
      <description>stephengold          Thank you for agreeing to be interviewed.
First question: Do you remember when you first encountered JMonkeyEngine? What was your first impression?
 danielperano          I started learning jME back in the 3.0 days, as I recall, and I was impressed with the features it offered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sgold interviews Jayfella</title>
      <link>/blog/interview-jayfella/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/interview-jayfella/</guid>
      <description>stephengold          Thank you for agreeing to be interviewed.
First question: When did you first hear about JMonkeyEngine?
 jayfella          Way back in 2014, after a long period of developing desktop applications, servers, and minecraft plugins, I decided to look into writing games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minie Physics Library Version 1.4 Released!</title>
      <link>/blog/minie14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/minie14/</guid>
      <description>Minie version 1.4 is an exciting new add-on for the JMonkeyEngine (JME) game engine.
  Minie provides an open-source physics engine for desktop games. It gives software developers using JME access to the proven technology of the Bullet Physics SDK version 2.89, including:
 rigid-body dynamics, soft bodies, collision detection, vehicle and character controllers, ray and sweep tests, and dynamic constraints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBR Tutorial</title>
      <link>/blog/pbr_tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/pbr_tutorial/</guid>
      <description>A continuing YouTube series helping users take leap from using the regular Lighting.j3md material to PbrLighting.j3md.
First part of my tutorial series in which I explain how to use jmonkeyengine&amp;rsquo;s Physically Based Rendering pipeline. Intended for people who already understand how to use the regular Lighting.j3md shader, but have no idea how PBR works.
Second part of my tutorial series in which I explain how to use jmonkeyengine&amp;rsquo;s Physically Based Rendering pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
